Cross-Examination is a drama, mystery film directed by Richard Thorpe.
Defense Atorney Gerald Waring uses great skill and ingenuity in his efforts to
save the life of a young man charged with the murder of his father.
Witness after witness piles up damaging evidence against the accused youth, but expert cross-examination by Waring digs out the
startling truth behind the killing and subsequently reveals the identity of the real killer in a surprise-twist ending.
Gerald Waring, played by H.B. Warner.
David Wells, played by Don Dillaway.
Emory Wells, played by William V. Mong.
Grace Varney, played by Sally Blane.
Mary Stevens, played by Sarah Padden.
Inez Wells, played by Natalie Moorhead.
Cross-Examination is a 1932 American drama film
directed by Richard Thorpe and starring H.
Warner, Sally Blane and Natalie Moorhead.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.